<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Oinky's Stuff]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>lib\media\favicon.png</url><title>Oinky's Stuff</title><link/></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 14:58:27 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="lib\rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 14:58:26 GMT</pubDate><copyright><![CDATA[oinky (oinkratpig)]]></copyright><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator>oinky (oinkratpig)</dc:creator><item><title><![CDATA[Terminology]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3377916758" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link" href="https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3377916758" target="_blank">Steam Guide</a><br>
Last updated December 5 2024<br><br><br><br>It's very confusing that one of her powers is called Chase considering chasing is a major mechanic in the game. I will be referring to it at "Dash" in this guide to avoid confusion.<br><br>The name of Houndmaster's hound.<br><br><br><br>Search is very, very helpful for map movement - but there's a huge mistake many Houndmasters make. You, for the most part, DO NOT want to send Snug to generators.<br>Sending Snug to a location is somewhat of a commitment. If at any point you see something interesting and want to divert from the Search path, Snug will still remain on that path and be unavailable for a significant time. It is better to send Snug to places where you know with 100% certainty that you will commit to the entire path.<br>Send Snug out repeatedly for short distances. Since there is virtually no cooldown for Search, you are not punished whatsoever for spamming it. Use it to walk multiple short distances.<br>If there is a generator that is high progress and you want to be there ASAP, obviously feel free to send Snug to the generator and follow the Search Path.<br><br>Dash is, ironically, is a better method of searching than Search. While redirecting, any survivors nearby will be highlighted with Killer Instinct INCLUDING survivors in lockers.<br>If you think there may be survivors nearby, send out a Dash and then immediately redirect. Look for Killer Instincts and then cancel the Dash.  <br><br><br><br><br>Chasing within loops as Houndmaster is quite difficult, but you have one huge, underrated strength - diverting attention. The human brain can only focus on one thing at once, and there happen to be two aggressors that survivors need to worry about.<br>Sending out Snug will cause it to immediately occupy the survivor's mind. They may remember your location, but attention will be on Snug rather than you. You can use this to your advantage and and intentionally avoid redirection to cause confusion. In the survivor's mind, they're expecting a redirect - they will not be focused on you gaining distance.<br>When sending a diversion, it is highly recommended to close in on the survivor while waiting for Snug to get in position for a redirect. Avoid standing still and focusing on Snug - move towards the survivor while looking at him.<br><br>Unfortunately, Snug is really easy to dodge. It takes less than a second to duck behind cover when they see a redirect coming. It is highly advised to plan ahead of time the angle your redirect will take, and then redirect -&gt; flick -&gt; send IMMEDIATELY. There should be minimal time between taking control of a redirect and sending it out to lower the chances of survivors reacting to it.<br>Obviously, if there is no cover near the survivor, you are free to take your time. But if the survivor's smart, they will always be near cover in case you Dash.<br><br>If you play every loop expecting to get a hit with Dash, the survivors will simply just dodge every attack. This is the most common-sense thing to do when playing Houndmaster, and survivors are aware of this.<br>Most Houndmasters will aim around loops as pictured, with the goal to land a hit with a redirect. This is, however, very predictable and easy to dodge. Instead, send out a single Dash but do not redirect. The survivor will predict a redirect and attempt to dodge, but it will never come. They will lose significant distance, allowing you to catch up. If you want to be particularly convincing, start a redirect but immediately cancel it. Survivors will see that you have possessed the dog to redirect and almost certainly make a dodging attempt, even if they are smart.<br><img src="https://i.imgur.com/ce20NEU.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer"><br><br>If the survivor is smart, after Dash is used they will always run to their perceived safest place to stand. This is often as far away from Snug, with as many obstacles between them and Snug as possible.<br>One example of survivor positioning:<br>
<img src="https://i.imgur.com/HrqKJHS.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer"><br>In this image, the killer is on the edge of a wall and last saw a survivor running past a pallet along the side of the aisles. Since there's a window in the middle, it may be tempting to send a Dash so that a redirect can attack along the entire aisle. This would be true for a normal M1 killer, as the window aisle would be the safest area - but once you send out Snug, the survivor will immediately see that aisle as dangerous. They will likely run out of the aisle and out to the back wall. Instead, it's recommended to send out Snug to the very back side of the aisle. They, standing in the window aisle, will assume you're going to send Snug in the aisle they were standing in, and run outside to safety - but that's actually where you sent it.<br><br>Snug's Dash can actually vault one-way windows backwards! (Vaults that lead to a drop-down where you cannot vault from the opposite side)<br><br>Search unfortunately disables in chase, but that doesn't mean it's useless. If you're at a large tile and chase has not started yet, you can use Search to increase your movement speed along the tile. Just avoid triggering the chase until you've caught up.<br><br><br>Houndmaster is very, very buggy. But some of the bugs are able to be played around.<br><br>Sometimes when returning from a Search, Snug will stay right behind you - just far enough away that the cooldown won't begin. To fix this, there are two possible solutions:<br>
<br>Let go of forward movement for any amount of time. Snug will catch up immediately.

<br>Pro(s): Fastest way for Snug to catch up (cooldown begins faster).
<br>Con(s): Decent amount of distance lost.
<br>Conclusion: Use if you need the cooldown back ASAP.


<br>Strafe side-to-side while moving forward. You will lose slight distance, allowing Snug to catch up.

<br>Pro(s): Minimal distance lost.
<br>Con(s): Might take a bit longer for Snug to catch up.
<br>Conclusion: Use if you don't care about the cooldown refreshing immediately.


<br><br><br>Houndmaster is very good in some situations and completely unusable in others. Having perks that mitigate her massive weaknesses are essential. Here is her "shopping list":<br>
<br>She needs gen regression (like every other killer).
<br>She needs help working around "impossible" tiles.
<br><br>Covers "impossible" tiles and both types of problem maps: large and multi-story.<br>
<br>Brutal Strength
<br>Superior Anatomy
<br>Surge
<br>Scourge Hook: Pain Resonance
<br><br>Tiers are defined as the following:<br>
<br>S Tier: Meta (recommended for optimal build).
<br>A Tier: Great substitutes for meta - not as good as S Tier, but close.
<br>B Tier: Good, but outclassed by other options.
<br>C Tier: Usable but not recommended if goal is to win.
<br>D Tier: Recommended against using.
<br>F Tier: Highly recommended against using.
<br><br>
<br>Bamboozle / Superior Anatomy

<br>There are many tiles where Dash cannot be used effectively due to vaults. Helps counter those tiles.


<br>Brutal Strength

<br>There are many maps in which predropping and pallet camping absolutely destroys her. This helps alleviate the issue.
<br>There are many tiles that Dash cannot be used effectively in any way. Helps chew threw pallets faster.
<br>Catching up quickly means the survivor is more vulnerable to Dash before making it to a loop.


<br>Scourge Hook: Pain Resonance

<br>Large maps can be very painful. Helps pressure gens that are far from the player that you otherwise wouldn't be able to reach in time.


<br>Surge

<br>Extremely helpful on multi-story maps, which she struggles on heavily due to bugs.
<br>Nearly all hits can proc Surge because Houndmaster uses almost exclusively basic attacks (not counting Snug vault hits).


<br><br>
<br>Dead Man's Switch

<br>Great in general due to the absurd amount of blocking time.
<br>Works well with Surge.


<br>Oppression

<br>Large maps can be very, very painful. Helps pressure gens that are far from the player that you otherwise wouldn't be able to reach in time.
<br>Does not trigger gen regression events on far gens, which is great.


<br><br><br>Ranking will be made using as much evidence as possible. If not enough evidence has been found yet, rankings may be blank.<br><br>Tiers are defined as the following:<br>
<br>S Tier: Consistent. High value.
<br>A Tier: Consistent. Medium value.
<br>B Tier: Consistent. Low value.
<br>C Tier: Inconsistent. High value.
<br>D Tier: Inconsistent. Medium value.
<br>F Tier: Bad/useless.
<br><br><br>Increases Snug's chase speed.<br>
<br>F Tier
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lHiLRwmgNXE" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lHiLRwmgNXE" target="_blank">Comparison shown here</a>. Seems to do literally nothing. If it does have an affect, it is so small it is unnoticeable.
<br><br>Increases Houndsense duration.<br>
<br>??? Tier
<br>Reasoning for tier.
<br><br>Increases movement speed along Search Path.<br>
<br>??? Tier
<br>Reasoning for tier.
<br><br>Decreases Snug's stun duration. Enduring for da doggy.<br>
<br>A Tier
<br>If the survivor runs to another tile immediately after stunning, the cooldown should be back in time to punish. If the survivor stays, cooldown comes back quickly. Solid.
<br><br><br>Aura reveal after Houndsense ends.<br>
<br>??? Tier
<br>Reasoning for tier.
<br><br>Reduced power cooldown.<br>
<br>A Tier
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lHiLRwmgNXE" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lHiLRwmgNXE" target="_blank">Comparison shown here.</a> Saves about 0.5s which is not amazing but also not terrible.
<br><br>Reduces cooldown of attacks made while survivor is grabbed by Snug.<br>
<br>B Tier
<br>The cooldown is pretty not-great but it will be happening very, very consistently.
<br><br>Survivors found with Search become Oblivious.<br>
<br>??? Tier
<br>Reasoning for tier.
<br><br>Increases Dash distance (does not affect redirect).<br>
<br>??? Tier
<br>Reasoning for tier.
<br><br><br>Increases redirect Dash distance.<br>
<br>??? Tier
<br>Reasoning for tier.
<br><br>Survivors found with Search become Exhausted.<br>
<br>??? Tier
<br>Reasoning for tier.
<br><br>Reveal survivor aura after stunning Snug.<br>
<br>A Tier
<br>Surprisingly useful. The aura reveal lasts quite a while.
<br><br>Inflict Mangled and Hemorrhage when hitting a survivor grabbed by Snug.<br>
<br>??? Tier
<br>Reasoning for tier.
<br><br>Survivors affected by Houndsense scream periodically but do not reveal their location.<br>
<br>??? Tier
<br>Reasoning for tier.
<br><br><br>Monitor &amp; Abuse but affected by Snug. While Snug is following, TR increased. While away, TR decreased.<br>
<br>??? Tier
<br>Reasoning for tier.
<br><br>Survivors near a survivor grabbed by Snug are inflicted with Houndsense.<br>
<br>??? Tier
<br>Reasoning for tier.
<br><br>Increases Snug's chase speed after a generator is completed. Activates permanently during endgame.<br>
<br>??? Tier
<br>Reasoning for tier.
<br><br>Increases break speed whenever a survivor is inflicted with Houndsense.<br>
<br>??? Tier
<br>Reasoning for tier.
<br><br><br>Aura reveal while redirecting Snug that persists after cancelling.<br>
<br>??? Tier
<br>Reasoning for tier.
<br><br>Increases the time Snug lingers at the Search destination. While Snug is away, Houndmaster gains Undetectable unless she is standing on the Search Path.<br>
<br>??? Tier
<br>Reasoning for tier.
]]></description><link>games\dead-by-daylight\houndmaster-guide.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Games/Dead by Daylight/Houndmaster Guide.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[oinky (oinkratpig)]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 14:56:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://i.imgur.com/ce20NEU.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="https://i.imgur.com/ce20NEU.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[index]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>helo welcome<br>use the table of contents and stuff ]]></description><link>index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">index.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[oinky (oinkratpig)]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 19:46:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Chase]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br>Perks that assist in chase or downing survivors.<br>
<br>All-Shaking Thunder

<br>Longer lunge.


<br>Bamboozle

<br>Locks down vaults.


<br>Batteries Included

<br>Faster movement speed.


<br>Beast of Prey

<br>Auto-mindgames in long chases.


<br>Blood Echo

<br>Exhaustion after hook.


<br>Bloodhound

<br>Mid-chase tracking vs. injured survivors.


<br>Brutal Strength

<br>Break pallets faster, meaning catching up is faster.


<br>Coup de Grace

<br>Longer lunge.


<br>Cruel Limits

<br>Automatic vault blocking.


<br>Dark Arrogance

<br>Faster vault at the cost of longer stuns.


<br>Dissolution

<br>Automatic pallet breaking.


<br>Dragon's Grip

<br>Exposing on generator touch.


<br>Enduring

<br>Shorter pallet stuns.


<br>Fire Up

<br>Faster at doing a lot of things (most importantly breaking pallets).


<br>Forced Hesitation

<br>Punish grouped-up survivors.


<br>Forced Penance

<br>Forces survivors to be injured.


<br>Friends 'til the End

<br>Exposing obsession.


<br>Game Afoot

<br>Faster chases vs. the obsession.


<br>Genetic Limits

<br>Exhaustion on injure.


<br>HEX: Blood Favor

<br>Pallet blocking.


<br>HEX: Crowd Control

<br>Vault blocking.


<br>HEX: Devour Hope

<br>Exposing and movement speed.


<br>HEX: Haunted Ground

<br>Exposing on totem cleanse..


<br>HEX: No One Escapes Death

<br>Exposing during endgame.


<br>HEX: The Third Seal

<br>Counters survivors' mid-chase aura perks (such as Windows of Opportunity).


<br>HEX: Two Can Play

<br>Pallet/vault blinds may result in survivor pathing to wrong areas.


<br>Hubris

<br>Exposing on stun/blind.


<br>Human Greed

<br>A well-placed chest at a tile will provide permanent wallhacks.


<br>I'm All Ears

<br>Mid-chase wallhacks.


<br>Iron Maiden

<br>Exposing on locker leave.


<br>Languid Touch

<br>Exhaustion on crow disturb.


<br>Machine Learning

<br>MUCH faster movement speed.


<br>Make Your Choice

<br>Exposing on unhook.


<br>Fearmonger

<br>Exhaustion on leaving generator.


<br>Nemesis

<br>Short wallhacks after stun.


<br>No Quarter

<br>Force survivor(s) to stay injured on missed skillcheck.


<br>Play With Your Food

<br>Movement speed.


<br>Rancor

<br>Exposing obsession at endgame + mori.


<br>Rapid Brutality

<br>Movement speed after hit.


<br>Save the Best for Last

<br>Faster weapon wipe animation.


<br>Septic Touch

<br>Exhaustion on nearby heals and counters mid-chase aura perks (such as Windows of Opportunity).


<br>Shadowborn

<br>Movement speed after blinded.


<br>Spirit Fury

<br>Instant pallet breaks.


<br>Starstruck

<br>Exposing nearby survivors while carrying.


<br>Stridor

<br>Easier tracking survivors mid-chase.


<br>Superior Anatomy

<br>Much faster vaulting.


<br>Terminus

<br>Permanent injures end-game.


<br>THWACK!

<br>Mid-chase tracking.


<br>Unbound

<br>Movement speed after injuring and vaulting.


<br>Unrelenting

<br>Faster miss cooldown.


<br>Weave Attunement

<br>Wallhacks on tiles with a dropped item.


<br>Zanshin Tactics

<br>Wallhacks after survivor drops a pallet.


<br><br><br>Perks that give you information outside of chase.<br>
<br>A Nurse's Calling

<br>Nearby healing survivors.


<br>Alien Instinct

<br>Farthest injured survivor after hooking.


<br>Awakened Awareness

<br>Survivors nearby while carrying survivor.


<br>Barbecue &amp; Chili

<br>Far-away survivors after hooking.


<br>Bitter Murmur

<br>All survivors after a generator is completed.


<br>Bloodhound

<br>Better blood tracking.


<br>Call of Brine

<br>Notifies if a recently-kicked generator is being worked on.


<br>Coulrophobia

<br>Very likely to reveal nearby healing survivors due to missed skillchecks.


<br>Darkness Revealed

<br>All survivors near every locker after Killer opens one.


<br>Dead Man's Switch

<br>Blocked gen's aura is shown in white.


<br>Deadlock

<br>Gen it has activated on is shown in white.


<br>Deathbound

<br>Far-away survivors after healing.


<br>Deerstalker

<br>Slugs.


<br>Discordance

<br>Multiple survivors working on one gen.


<br>Dragon's Grip

<br>Scream when marked generator is touched.


<br>Eruption

<br>Screamy when boom-boom.


<br>Friends 'til the End

<br>Location of one survivor after hook.


<br>Gearhead

<br>Generators being repaired are revealed after someone is damaged.


<br>Grim Embrace

<br>Obsession after full stacks reached.


<br>HEX: Face the Darkness

<br>AAAAAA! AAAAAAAAAA! AAAAA!


<br>HEX: Huntress' Lullaby

<br>More failed skillchecks, therefore more info.


<br>HEX: Retribution

<br>On hex totem cleanse.


<br>Hoarder

<br>On item pickup.


<br>Human Greed

<br>Near a chest.


<br>Infectious Fright

<br>Near the Killer after downing someone.


<br>Iron Maiden

<br>Leaving a locker.


<br>Lethal Pursuer

<br>Start of match.


<br>Merciless Storm

<br>Failed skillchecks.


<br>Nowhere to Hide

<br>Near gen after it is kicked.


<br>Oppression

<br>Failed skillcheck.


<br>Overcharge

<br>Failed skillcheck.


<br>Predator

<br>Broke chase.


<br>Rancor

<br>After generator is completed.


<br>Scourge Hook: Floods of Rage

<br>After unhooked from Scourge Hook.


<br>Scourge Hook: Hangman's Trick

<br>Near Scourge Hook while someone is being carried.


<br>Scourge Hook: Jagged Compass

<br>Highest-progress gen after hooked on Scourge Hook.


<br>Spies from the Shadows

<br>Disturbed a crow.


<br>Stridor

<br>Louder breathing sounds.


<br>Surveillance

<br>Generator stops regressing + gen repair sounds.


<br>Territorial Imperative

<br>Went into basement.


<br>Thrilling Tremors

<br>Working on a gen.


<br>THWACK!

<br>Near Killer after they break a pallet/wall.


<br>Tinkerer

<br>When almost done with gen.


<br>Trail of Torment

<br>Revealed on deactivation.


<br>Ultimate Weapon

<br>Near Killer after opening a locker.


<br>Unnerving Presence

<br>Failed skillchecks.


<br>Weave Attunement

<br>Near an item on the ground.


<br>Whispers

<br>Near the Killer.


<br><br><br>Perks that slow the game down for the survivors, allowing more time for the Killer.<br>
<br>Blood Echo

<br>Healing interrupts reset progress.


<br>Call of Brine

<br>Faster generator regression (worthless, but technically true).


<br>Corrupt Intervention

<br>Early-game slowdown.


<br>Coulrophobia

<br>Slower healing and harder skillchecks.


<br>Dead Man's Switch

<br>Blocks one generator at a time for a very, very long duration.


<br>Deadlock

<br>Blocks highest-progress gen after one is completed.


<br>Dominance

<br>Blocks chests and totems.


<br>Dying Light

<br>Slower repair speed every hook (does not affect obsession).


<br>Eruption

<br>Explodes all marked gens when someone is downed.


<br>Grim Embrace

<br>Blocks all gens if someone is hooked for the first time.


<br>HEX: Huntress' Lullaby

<br>Harder skillchecks.


<br>HEX: Pentimento

<br>Punish cleansing totems with slower action speeds.


<br>HEX: Ruin

<br>Automatic regression.


<br>HEX: The Third Seal

<br>Blindness makes finding things harder/slower.


<br>HEX: Thrill of the Hunt

<br>Slower to cleanse totems.


<br>HEX: Undying

<br>Force an extra totem cleanse.


<br>HEX: Wretched Fate

<br>Obsession is useless until cleansed.


<br>Knockout

<br>Slugs are much harder to pick up.


<br>Leverage

<br>Healing on hook is much slower.


<br>Merciless Storm

<br>Missed MS skillchecks block the gen for a while.


<br>Fearmonger

<br>Blindness makes finding things harder/slower.


<br>No Quarter

<br>Self-healing may result in all of that time being wasted.


<br>No Way Out

<br>Blocks exit gates.


<br>Oppression

<br>Mass regression and possible failed skillcheck(s).


<br>Overcharge

<br>Faster regression and possibility of a failed skillcheck.


<br>Pop Goes the Weasel

<br>Gen regression after every hook.


<br>Remember Me

<br>Slower exit gate progress (if not obsession).


<br>Scourge Hook: Gift of Pain

<br>Slower healing and slower repair speed if healed.


<br>Scourge Hook: Pain Resonance

<br>Highest-progress gen explodes when someone is hooked for the first time.


<br>Septic Touch

<br>Blindness makes finding things harder/slower.


<br>Sloppy Butcher

<br>Much slower healing and possibility of losing all progress.


<br>Surge

<br>Gens explode near Killer when survivor downed.


<br>Thanatophobia

<br>More injures = more slowdown.


<br>Thrilling Tremors

<br>Blocks gens after a survivor is picked up.


<br>Ultimate Weapon

<br>Blindness makes finding things harder/slower.


<br>Undone

<br>Not even worth writing about.


<br>Unnerving Presence

<br>Harder skillchecks.


<br><br><br>Perks that give the Killer stealth capabilities.<br>
<br>Alien Instinct

<br>Farthest injured survivor is oblivious.


<br>Dark Devotion

<br>Terror radius transfers to obsession.


<br>Deathbound

<br>Oblivious after healing.


<br>Furtive Chase

<br>Stealth after hooking obsession.


<br>HEX: Plaything

<br>Oblivious after being hooked.


<br>Hysteria

<br>All injured survivors oblivious after someone is injured.


<br>Insidious

<br>Camping stealth.


<br>Machine Learning

<br>Stealth after marked gen is completed.


<br>Monitor &amp; Abuse

<br>Passive, small stealth affect.


<br>Tinkerer

<br>Stealth when generator is almost completed.


<br>Trail of Torment

<br>Stealth after kicking gen. Able to be deactivated by survivors.


<br>Unforeseen

<br>Stealth after kicking gen. Active for a fixed amount of time then disables.


<br><br><br>Perks that make small things feel better.<br>
<br>Agitation

<br>Faster carrying movement speed.


<br>Franklin's Demise

<br>Don't have to worry about items.


<br>Iron Grasp

<br>Much less likely to have survivors wiggle off.


<br>Iron Maiden

<br>Lockers are basically out of the question for survivors.


<br>Lethal Pursuer

<br>Immediately know where to go at the start of the game.


<br>Lightborn

<br>Don't have to worry about flashlights.


<br>Mad Grit

<br>Don't have to worry about protection hits while carrying.


<br>Overwhelming Presence

<br>Don't have to worry about items.


<br>Shattered Hope

<br>Don't have to worry about boons.


<br>Unrelenting

<br>Missing is nearly unpunished.


<br>Zanshin Tactics

<br>All pallets/vaults are visible.


<br><br><br>Perks that are mostly useful after all of the generators have been completed.<br>
<br>Batteries Included

<br>Lots of completed generators during endgame.


<br>Blood Warden

<br>Punishes survivors staying when exit gates are open and someone is hooked.


<br>Fire Up

<br>Longer the game goes on, the stronger you become.


<br>HEX: No One Escapes Death

<br>Instant-downs during endgame.


<br>No Way Out

<br>Blocks exit gates.


<br>Rancor

<br>Instant-down/mori during endgame.


<br>Remember Me

<br>Much longer exit gate progression for everyone except obsession.


<br>Terminus

<br>Permanent injure during endgame.


<br><br><br>Perks that don't do much by themselves, but work great with other perks.<br>
<br>Agitation

<br>Carrying builds.


<br>Awakened Awareness

<br>Carrying builds.


<br>Distressing

<br>Terror Radius builds.


<br>Franklin's Demise

<br>Item builds.


<br>HEX: Huntress' Lullaby

<br>Skill check builds.


<br>Hoarder

<br>Item builds (or with some Killers <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GHulq9BAGDE" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GHulq9BAGDE" target="_blank">like Xenomorph</a>).


<br>Iron Grasp

<br>Carrying builds.


<br>Iron Maiden

<br>Builds or Killers that open lockers a lot.


<br>Lethal Pursuer

<br>Aura-revealing perks.


<br>Mad Grit

<br>Carrying builds.


<br>Monitor &amp; Abuse

<br>Addons that lower Terror Radius distance.


<br>Nemesis

<br>Obsession builds.


<br>Scourge Hook: Jagged Compass

<br>Scourge Hooks.


<br>Scourge Hook: Monstrous Shrine

<br>Basement builds.


<br>Undone

<br>Skill check builds.


<br>Unforeseen

<br>Terror Radius builds.


<br>Weave Attunement

<br>Item builds.


]]></description><link>games\dead-by-daylight\killer-perk-categories.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Games/Dead by Daylight/Killer Perk Categories.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[oinky]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 20:01:31 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>